{
    "subject": "resource/The_Crowning_Touch",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Crowning Touch is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9563292264938354,
            "question": "Is 'The Crowning Touch' a well-known film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7407418489456177,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Crowning Touch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4133266508579254,
            "question": "What other information could you tell me about 'The Crowning Touch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4100593030452728,
            "question": "Are there different types of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.409525603055954,
            "question": "What makes a film a specific type of film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3109460473060608,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of a film that is also a type of 'Film'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27289915084838867,
            "question": "What are some popular types of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09929842501878738,
            "question": "What are some common themes found in films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06401147693395615,
            "question": "How has the film industry changed over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0579046756029129,
            "question": "Can you name some famous directors who have made films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Crowning Touch is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6458_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the film industry changed over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6458_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes found in films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6458_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular types of films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6458_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6458_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The document mentions \"The Crowning Touch\" as a movie with details such as director, runtime, and cast. This confirms that \"The Crowning Touch\" is indeed a film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}